<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pages on The Edible Clinic</title>
    <link>https://the-edible-clinic.gitlab.io/page/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pages on The Edible Clinic</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <managingEditor>edibleclinic@gmail.com (The Edible Clinic)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>edibleclinic@gmail.com (The Edible Clinic)</webMaster>
    
	<atom:link href="https://the-edible-clinic.gitlab.io/page/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://the-edible-clinic.gitlab.io/page/photo-sharing-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>edibleclinic@gmail.com (The Edible Clinic)</author>
      <guid>https://the-edible-clinic.gitlab.io/page/photo-sharing-policy/</guid>
      <description>I love and appreciate when people share our content! However, please include a link back to the corresponding page on my site, listing full credit to The Edible Clinic. Use of our photos without our permission and without proper attribution is prohibited.
We do not allow our images to be directly monetized through affiliate marketing, whether on a website or social media platforms. Please contact us via email to seek permission for the use of any images outside of the guidelines listed above.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A little bit about us</title>
      <link>https://the-edible-clinic.gitlab.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>edibleclinic@gmail.com (The Edible Clinic)</author>
      <guid>https://the-edible-clinic.gitlab.io/about/</guid>
      <description>As physicians who like to inject a dose of healthy scepticism to the myriad of skincare products that are on the shelves, we found ourselves researching the ingredients of every skincare product we bought before applying it on our skin. We want to share all our safer, simplified skincare routines that we&amp;rsquo;ve landed on, as well as all the skincare formulations and tips we&amp;rsquo;ve discovered along the way. Stay tuned.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Follow us!</title>
      <link>https://the-edible-clinic.gitlab.io/follow/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>edibleclinic@gmail.com (The Edible Clinic)</author>
      <guid>https://the-edible-clinic.gitlab.io/follow/</guid>
      <description>Follow us on:
 Facebook Instagram Pinterest  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>https://the-edible-clinic.gitlab.io/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>edibleclinic@gmail.com (The Edible Clinic)</author>
      <guid>https://the-edible-clinic.gitlab.io/privacy/</guid>
      <description>We are committed to keeping your personal information safe. The following policy describes how your protected information is used and shared.
OVERVIEW
In order for us to operate our business and provide our services to you, it is sometimes necessary for us to collect or process information about you. In general terms, this information will take one or more of the following forms:
Information that you provide to us directly, such as in the situation where you complete an online form or send us a message via our website; Information that is automatically sent to us by your computer’s internet browser when you visit our website, such as your computer’s technical address (or ‘IP address’) or information about which particular internet browser you are using and so on; Information about how you use our website or our services, such as which pages you visit, how frequently you visit the site and so forth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why not send us a note?</title>
      <link>https://the-edible-clinic.gitlab.io/subscribe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>edibleclinic@gmail.com (The Edible Clinic)</author>
      <guid>https://the-edible-clinic.gitlab.io/subscribe/</guid>
      <description>You can subscribe to our newletter.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>